Guide to the Walter Francis White and Poppy Cannon Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Walter Francis White and Poppy Cannon papers
1910-1956
JWJ MSS 38
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
20.85
(46 boxes) + 4 broadside folders, 1 art object.
The Walter White and Poppy Cannon Papers document the careers and lives of Walter White and Poppy Cannon and span the dates 1910 to 1956. The Papers contain correspondence, writings, other papers, and photographs documenting Walter White's career as the Secretary for the N.A.A.C.P. and as a writer. Poppy Cannon's career as an editor, writer, and publicity consultant is also documented in the Papers.
White, Walter, 1893-1955
Cannon, Poppy, 1907-
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Walter White and Poppy Cannon, [195?] -1957.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research. Boxes 39-40: Restricted fragile material. Reference copies have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
WALTER FRANCIS WHITE, 1893-1955
Walter White was born in Atlanta, Georgia, on July 1, 1893. He was one of the seven children (he had five sisters and one brother) of George White, a Post Office employee, and his wife Madeline Harrison White. He completed high school in 1912 and entered Atlanta University, from which he graduated in 1916. While an undergraduate he had a variety of part-time jobs and was at one time a hotel porter. He later became an insurance salesman for the black-owned, Atlanta-based Standard Life Insurance Company. After graduation, White became a full-time clerk with that company. White was an active and energetic member of the Atlanta branch of the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (N.A.A.C.P.), which he served as secretary. Through his work for that organization he became acquainted with James Weldon Johnson, then Field Secretary and National Organizer for the Association. It was on Johnson's recommendation and at his urging that White consented to become one of the Associate Secretaries of the N.A.A.C.P. He served in this capacity from 1918 to 1929. White married one of the Association's office secretaries, Leah Gladys Powell, in 1922. During the twenties White became famous for his first-hand investigations of lynching, which he conducted by posing as a white man. He also published two novels, Fire in the Flint (1924) and Flight (1926), and an exposé of lynching, Rope and Faggot, A Biography of Judge Lynch (1928).
When James Weldon Johnson left the N.A.A.C.P., Walter White was made acting Secretary. With Johnson's final resignation, White succeeded to the permanent position in 1931. During his tenure as Secretary, from 1929 to 1955, White led the campaign against the confirmation of John J. Parker to the Supreme Court, directed the Association's activities in the Scottsboro case, and directed activities designed to thwart communist influence in the organization. He also consolidated the powers of the Secretary by exercising strong personal control over the national staff. From 1943 to 1945 White served as a war correspondent for the New York Post. He visited most of the major war areas and as a result of his experiences wrote A Rising Wind (1945). Later he expanded his public writings by producing an editorial column for several newspapers, including the Chicago Defender. In 1948 he published his autobiography, A Man Called White.
The years 1949 and 1950 were very active years for White. It was at this time that he carried out his plans to divorce Gladys Powell and marry Poppy Cannon, a white woman. Just prior to his marriage, he submitted his resignation to the N.A.A.C.P., but his letter of resignation was filed without being acted upon, though he was granted a year's leave of absence. There may have been a connection between his impending marriage and his attempted resignation, as he had kept his marriage plans a secret from the Association. Later White withdrew his resignation. While on leave of absence White married, participated in the 'Round the World Town Hall Meeting, and entered on an extensive lecture tour. During his leave there were two developments within the Association that were to face White on his return. The first was a feeling that the communists had again gained an undue influence in some branches of the Association. The second internal difficulty involved White himself. Many members of the local branches and of the national staff felt that White exercised too much power, and there was an attempt to oust him. Though he thwarted this attempt and retained the secretaryship, the office was stripped of some of its power. During the last five years of his life White increased those of his activities not related to the N.A.A.C.P. and the field of race relations. He became particularly interested in Haiti and the Caribbean, and sometimes acted as an unofficial spokesman for the interests of that area. White was likewise active on behalf of India and interested himself in its economic and political development. He cultivated the friendship of "Nan" Pandit, Nehru's sister, and made arrangements for Nehru to meet black leaders when he visited the United States. During the 1950's White was in declining health as the result of a heart ailment. He died of a heart attack on March 21, 1955.
Members of Walter White's Immediate Family:
George White - father
Madeline White - mother
George White - brother
Madeline White - sister
Alice White Glenn - sister
Helen Martin - sister
*Olive White - sister
Leah Gladys Powell White - first wife
*Walter Carl Darrow White - son called "Pidge" for le petit pigeon
Jane White - daughter
Poppy Cannon White - second wife
Cynthia Cannon - second Mrs. White's child
Alf Askland - second Mrs. White's child
Claudia Philippe - second Mrs. White's child
Charles Claudius Philippe - second Mrs. White's third husband
* No material in collection
POPPY CANNON, 1905-1975
Poppy Cannon was born Lillian Gruskin in Cape Town, South Africa, on August 2, 1905, the eldest of four children of Robert and Henrietta Gruskin. She came with her parents to the United States in 1908 and settled in Kittening, Pennsylvania, where her father ran a store. She won a scholarship to Vassar College and eventually became a journalist, food editor of Ladies' Home Journal, House Beautiful, Town and Country, and Mademoiselle, and the author of several cookbooks, including The Can Opener Cookbook, The Bride's Cookbook, The Presidents' Cookbook, Aromas and Flavors of the Past and Present (with Alice B. Toklas), and a memoir of her fourth husband, A Gentle Knight: My Husband Walter White. She first married Carl L. Cannon, who became Acquisitions Librarian at Yale in 1931, and bore a daughter Cynthia. Her second husband, the Norway-born Alf E. Askland, an investment counselor and the father of her only son, Jon Alf., died in 1939. In 1941 she married Charles Claudius Philippe, an executive at the Waldorf Hotel, whom she divorced in 1949 and with whom she had a daughter, Claudia. She married Walter F. White in 1949. She died in New York in April, 1975.
Scope and Contents
The Walter White and Poppy Cannon Papers document the careers and lives of Walter White and Poppy Cannon and span the dates 1910 to 1956. The Papers contain correspondence, writings, other papers, and photographs relating to Walter White's career as the Secretary for the N.A.A.C.P. and as a writer and to Poppy Cannon's career as an editor, writer, and publicity consultant.
Walter White's work for the N.A.A.C.P. and, more broadly, the development of the N.A.A.C.P. during his tenure, are recorded in the Papers. This includes, for example, the N.A.A.C.P.'s handling of the Scottsboro case, investigation of lynchings, response to communism, and increased legal action against discrimination.
The Papers also concern White's work outside of the N.A.A.C.P. including his writing career, lecture tours, and international work (most notably on behalf of the Republic of Haiti and India). Correspondence, research materials, drafts, publicity, and reviews document these activities and provide insight into White's creative process. As the Papers illustrate, White's writings range from journalism to prose, poetry, and non-fiction.
Poppy Cannon's career is also recorded in the Papers. In addition to material relating to her writings as a journalist, editor, and publicity consultant, the Papers also document Cannon's collaboration with White on various writing projects as well as her memoir of White ( A Gentle Knight ).
Walter White's and Poppy Cannon's professional and personal relationships with writers, publishers, friends and family are recorded in their correspondence. Correspondents include Josephine Baker, Mary McLeod Bethune, Dumarsais Estime, Oscar and Dorothy Hammerstein, William H. Hastie, John Haynes Holmes, James Weldon Johnson, Bill ("Bojangles") Robinson, Franklin D. and Eleanor Roosevelt, Harry S. Truman, Algernon Black, Norman Cousins, Vijaya Lakshmi Pandit, J. Waties Waring, and Roy Wilkins.
In addition the Papers provide insight into White's and Cannon's personal relationship, including courtship and marriage, and their experience as an interracial couple.
Arrangement
The Papers are organized into five series: Correspondence, Writings, National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (N.A.A.C.P.), Other Papers, and Photographs.
Appendix A: Former Call Number Reference
The index below provides a cross reference from the catalogue card numbers, noted as —#, to the current location of the same material in the present arrangement.
Walter White
1: Box 22, folders 195-200
2: Box 15, folders 145-146
3: Bsd 384
4: Box 15, folder 147
5: Box 16, folders 153-156
6: Box 16, folders 151-152
7: Box 16, folders 151-152
8: Box 15, folders 148-150
9: Bsd 385
10: Bsd 386
11: Boxes 22-23, folders 204-216
12: Boxes 22-23, folders 204-216
13: Box 17, folder 158
14: Box 17, folder 159-164
15: Box 18, folders 165-172
16: Box 19, folders 173-180
17: Box 20, folders 181-185
Misc. 18: Box 25, folder 236
Misc. 19: Box 25, folder 236
Misc. 20: Box 25, folder 237
Misc. 21: Box 25, folders 261-263
Misc. 22: Box 22, folder 191
Misc. 23: Box 25, folder 257
Misc. 24: Box 22, folder 192
Misc. 25: Box 22, folder 194
Misc. 26: Box 22, folder 201
Misc. 27: Box 22, folder 201
Misc. 28: Box 22, folder 201
Misc. 29: Box 25, folder 246
Misc. 30: Box 25, folder 245
Misc. 31: Box 25, folder 264
Misc. 32: Box 25, folder 247
Misc. 33: Box 25, folder 265
Misc. 34: Box 22, folder 202
Misc. 35: Box 22, folder 202
Misc. 36: Box 25, folder 250
Misc. 37: Box 25, folder 248
Misc. 38: Box 25, folder 248
Misc. 39: Box 25, folder 258
Misc. 40: Box 22, folder 193
Misc. 41: Box 22, folder 203
Misc. 42: Box 24, folder 217
Misc. 43: Box 25, folder 238
Misc. 44: Box 24, folder 218
Misc. 45: Box 25, folder 266
Misc. 46: Box 25, folder 267
Misc. 47: Box 25, folder 251
Misc. 48: Box 25, folder 252
Misc. 49: Box 24, folder 219
Misc. 50: Box 25, folder 240-241
Misc. 51: Box 24, folder 220
Misc. 52: Box 24, folder 221
Misc. 53: Box 24, folder 221
Misc. 54: Box 24, folder 221
Misc. 55: Box 34, folder 356
Misc. 56: Box 25, folders 261-263
Misc. 57: Box 24, folder 228
Misc. 58: Boxes 35-36, folders 359-371
Misc. 59: Box 24, folders 222-227
Misc. 60: Box 24, folder 229
Misc. 61: Box 24, folder 229
Misc. 62: Box 24, folder 229
Misc. 63:
Misc. 64: Box 24, folder 230
Misc. 65: Box 24, folder 230
Misc. 66: Box 24, folder 230
Misc. 67: Box 24, folder 230
Misc. 68: Box 25, folder 268
Misc. 69: Box 25, folder 239
Misc. 70: Box 24, folder 231
Misc. 71: Box 25, folder 244
Misc. 72: Box 25, folder 269
Misc. 73: Box 25, folder 255
Misc. 74: Box 25, folder 242
Misc. 75: Box 25, folder 243
Misc. 76: Box 25, folder 270
Misc. 77: Box 25, folder 253
Misc. 78: Box 25, folder 259
Misc. 79: Box 24, folder 232
Misc. 80: Box 25, folder 254
Misc. 81: Box 25, folder 271
Misc. 82: Box 25, folder 272
Misc. 83: Box 25, folder 256
Misc. 84: Box 25, folder 256
Misc. 85: Box 24, folder 233
Misc. 86: Box 24, folder 233
Misc. 87: Box 24, folder 234
Misc. 88: Box 24, folder 235
Misc. 89: Box 24, folder 235
Misc. 90: Box 24, folder 235
Misc. 91: Box 24, folder 235
Misc. 92: Box 24, folder 235
Misc. 93: Box 25, folder 261-263
Misc. 94: Box 25, folder 261-263
Misc. 95: Box 20, folder 186
Misc. 96: Box 20, folder 186
Misc. 97: Box 20, folder 187
Misc. 98: Box 21, folder 188-190
Misc. 99: Bsd 387
Misc. 100: Box 27, folder 282
Misc. 101: Box 27, folder 288-289
Misc. 102: Box 27, folder 290
Misc. 103: Box 27, folders 283-287
Misc. 104: Box 27, folder 291
Misc. 105: Box 28, folder 292
Misc. 106: Box 28, folder 293
Misc. 107: Box 28, folder 294
Misc. 108: Box 27, folders 283-287
Misc. 109:
Misc. 110: Box 27, folders 283-287
Misc. 111: Box 28, folder 295
Misc. 112: Box 28, folder 296
Misc. 113: Box 28, folder 297
Poppy Cannon
1: Box 29, folder 298
2: Box 29, folders 299-301
3: Box 29, folders 302-304
4: Box 29, folder 305
5: Box 29, folders 306-309
6: Box 30, folders 310-312
7: Box 31, folder 322
8: Box 30, folders 313-314
9: Box 30, folders 313-314
10: Box 30, folders 313-314
11: Box 30, folders 313-314
12: Box 30, folders 315-317
13: Box 31, folders 318-320
14: Box 31, folder 321
15: Box 33, folder 352
16: Box 33, folder 353
17: Box 33, folder 354
18: Box 33, folder 355
19: Box 33, folder 355
20: Box 32, folders 326-333
21: Box 32, folders 334-342
Misc. 22: Box 32, folder 323
Misc. 23: Box 33, folder 348
Misc. 24: Box 33, folder 348
Misc. 25: Box 33, folder 348
Misc. 26: Box 38, folder 389
Misc. 27: Box 32, folder 324
Misc. 28: Box 33, folder 343
Misc. 29: Box 33, folder 343
Misc. 30: Box 38, folder 390
Misc. 31: Box 33, folder 344
Misc. 32: Box 33, folder 345
Misc. 33: Box 33, folder 349
Misc. 34: Box 32, folder 325
Misc. 35: Box 33, folder 350
Misc. 36: Box 33, folder 346
Misc. 37: Box 37, folder 382
Misc. 38: Box 33, folder 351
Misc. 39: Box 33, folder 347
Misc. 40: Box 37, folder 372
Appendix B: Select Subject Guide to the Correspondence
Please note that the subject references below are to the Walter White Correspondence subseries (WW) and the Poppy Cannon Correspondence subseries (PCW).
American Red Cross, discrimination in during WW II
See: American Red Cross (WW)
Armed forces, blacks in
----See: Brown, Mary (WW)
----Hurston, Zora Neal (WW)
---- Look Magazine (WW)
----Roosevelt, Franklin D. (WW)
----White, George (father of WW) (WW)
----Wilkins, Roy (WW)
Armed forces, peace time conscription and discrimination in
----See: Wilkins, Roy (WW)
Atlanta University, presidency of
----See: Martin, Eugene (WW)
Atomic energy research, blacks in
----See: Wallace, Hershel D. (WW)
Baker, Josephine, discrimination against at Stork Club
----See: Baker, Josephine (WW)
Caribbean, Trujillo as agressor, British empire in, political movements in,
----See: Davenport (WW)
---- Look Magazine (WW)
Civil Rights, Congress and
----See: White, Walter (1949) (PCW)
Civil Rights, economic pressure used against blacks
----See: Eisenhower, Dwight David (WW)
Civil Rights, legislation
----See: Mitchell, Clarence (WW)
----Moon Henry Lee (WW)
----Tobias, Channing (WW)
Civil Rights, "The Power of Civil Rights, National and International"
----speech by Walter White
----See: Methodist Youth Movement (WW)
Colonialism
----See: Reid, Helen Rogers (WW)
----Roper, Joseph James (WW)
----Bunche, Ralph (WW)
----Columbia Broadcasting - Nicholson, Sigmund (WW)
Colonialism
----See: White, Walter 1946 Jul 30 (PCW)
----White, Walter (1948) (PCW)
----White, Walter (1949) (PCW)
Communist Party, infiltration of N.A.A.C.P., actions against infiltration
----See: Current, Gloster B. (WW)
----Pickens, William (WW)
----Roosevelt, Eleanor (WW)
Dominican Republic
----See: Dominican Republic - Zeisburg, Carl (WW)
----Trujillo, Rafael Molinas (WW)
----Trujillo, Rafael Molinas - untitled, hand-written article
----[by Walter White?] (WW)
Du Bois, W.E.B., relations with the N.A.A.C.P. (1948)
----See: Marshall, Thurgood (WW)
Encyclopedia of the Negro
----See: Stokes, Anson Phelps (WW)
Eternal Light Program, Walter White's remarks at
----See: White, Walter 1949 Feb. 6 (PCW)
Fair Employment Practices Commission Bill, N.A.A.C.P. action in favor of
----See: Mitchell, Clarence (WW)
----Moon, Henry Lee (WW)
Fire in the Flint, by Walter White
----See: Alfred A. Knopf Inc.(WW)
A Gentle Knight, by Poppy Cannon
----See: Rinehart & Co., Inc. (PCW)
Ghana, independence of
----See: Hoffman, Henry (PCW)
Haiti, publicity and propaganda, internal development
----See: Charles, Joseph D. (WW)
----Dulles, John Foster (WW)
----Estime, Dumarsais (WW)
----Orchard, Thomas (WW)
----Truman, Harry S. (WW)
Haiti, publicity and propaganda, internal development
----See: Haiti (PCW)
Haitian--United States relations
----See: Chatelet des Fleurs, Grace (PCW)
Harlem, proposed picture book of
----See: Buchanan, Charles (WW)
"Has Science Conquered the Color Line? by Walter White, reader reaction to
----See: Look Magazine (WW)
----Reader's Letters (WW)
----note: other responses are filed in the General correspondence
Hawaii, prejudice against black soldiers
----See: White, George (WW)
How Far The Promised Land, by Walter White
----See: Viking Press (WW) (PCW)
How Far the Promised Land, by Walter White
----See: Poppy Cannon General Correspondence (PCW)
House Committee on Un-American Activities, G. Bromley Oxnam's appearance
----before
----See: Oxnam, G. Bromley (WW)
Huggins, Molly, "Lady Molly of Jamaica, or Mrs. Roosevelt of the Caribbean, or The Caribbean's Mrs. Roosevelt," by Poppy Cannon
----See: Huggins, Molly (PCW)
"I love you, God," by Poppy Cannon (three pages)
----See: re: Wright, Louis Tompkins (PCW)
India, United States relations with, development of, publicity
----and promotion, farm machines for
----See: Acheson, Dean (WW)
----Amherst College (WW)
----British Information Service (WW)
----Byfield, Robert (WW)
----Ford, Henry (WW)
----Hare, Raymond A. (WW)
----India (WW)
----McKormick, Fowler (WW)
----Nehru, Jawaharlal (WW)
----Pandit, Vijaya Laskshimi (WW)
----Roosevelt, Eleanor (WW)
----Roper, Elmo (WW)
----Ryan, Joseph James (WW)
----Seabrook, C. F. (WW)
----Sampson, Edith (WW)
----Truman, Harry S. (WW)
"Intoxicating Liquors Strictly Prohibited," by Walter White article
----(4 pages) sent to the New Yorker
----See: New Yorker (WW)
James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection
----See: Edwin Embree (WW)
James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection
----See: Carl Van Vechten (PCW)
----
Juvenile delinquents, nutrition and genes
----See: Elwood, C. (WW)
Ku Klux Klan
----See: McLeod, Thomas (WW)
Labor, Mississippi levee jobs, blacks and
----See: Alexander, Will W., filed Aa-Amer. Fa (WW)
----Williamson, John M., filed Wi-Wz (WW)
Lee, Lionel Cornelius Canegata (Canada)
----See: Miller, Lucile V. (WW)
Lodge amendment to the Constitution of the United States, effect
----on black voters
----See: Mitchell, Clarence (WW)
Lynchings and anti-lynching legislation
----See: McLeod, Thomas G. (WW)
----Pan-African Congress (WW)
----Roosevelt, Franklin (WW)
"Lysistrata Local" script by Walter White and Poppy Cannon,
----correspondence about
----See: Walter White (1946) (PCW)
McBride, Mary Margaret, proposed broadcast from Virgin Islands
----See: Walter White (1947) (PCW)
"Madam Ambassador--the First One," [by Poppy Cannon?]
----See: Pandit, Vijaya Lakshimi (PCW)
A Man Called White, by Walter White
----See: Viking Press (WW) (PCW)
Minstrel shows
----See: Urban League of Portland (WW)
Motion Pictures, black in
----See: Ayres, Lew (WW)
----Schary, Dore (WW)
----Zanuck, Darryl F. (WW)
----Rivkin, Allan (WW)
----Marshall, Thurgood (WW)
N.A.A.C.P., infiltration by Communist Party, actions against infiltration
----See: Current, Gloster B. (WW)
----Pickens, William (WW)
----Roosevelt, Eleanor (WW)
N.A.A.C.P., membership drive
----See: Walter White to Oliver Harrington 1946 Nov 5 (PCW)
----enclosed in Walter White to Poppy Cannon
----1946 Nov 25
N.A.A.C.P., the secretaryship (1950)
----See: Christopher, Nathan K. (WW)
----Dejoie, C. C. (WW)
----Durham, Barbee W. (WW)
----Marshall, Thurgood (WW)
----Roosevelt, Eleanor (WW)
----Spingarn, Arthur B. (WW)
----Weber, Palmer (WW)
----White, Poppy Cannon (1950) (WW)
----Wilkins, Roy (WW)
----Wilkins, Mrs. Roy (WW)
N.A.A.C.P., the secretaryship (1950)
----See: White, Walter (PCW)
N.A.A.C.P., Walter White's appointment to national office
----See: James Weldon Johnson (WW)
"The Negro and the High Court," by Walter White
----White's reaction to the editing of the article
----See: Nation (WW)
Nehru, Jawaharlal, visit to United States, meeting with blacks
----See: Nehru, Jawaharlal (WW)
----Pandit, Vijaya Lakshimi (WW)
Oxnam, G. Bromley, appearance before House Committee on Un-American Activities.
----See: Oxnam, G. Bromley (WW)
Puerto Rico
----See: Fernos-Isern A. (WW)
----Morin, Luis Munos (WW)
Photography, proposed picture book of Harlem
----See: Buchanan, Charles (WW)
"The Power of Civil Rights, National International speech by Walter White
----See: Methodist Youth Movement (WW)
"Priorities at Home, Negro in Human Relations" address by Mrs. J. Waties
----Waring
----See: Waring, J. Waites (WW)
Race relations, British views on American
----See: Pan-African Congress (WW)
----
Race relations, college fraternities
----See: Newcomb, George C. (WW)
Race relations, world press and
----See: Union For Democratic Action (WW)
Race riots
----See: Marshall, Thurgood (WW)
Randolph, Asa Philip, childhood of,
----See: Randolph, Asa Philip (WW)
Reuther, Walter P., correspondence related to testimonial dinner
----1949 Dec 16, and excerpts from Walter White's remarks
----See: re: Reuther, Walter P. (WW)
Robeson, Paul, communism and
----See: Bedlek, Suzy (WW)
----Robinson, William Albert Jr. (WW)
Robeson, Paul, Peekskill riot
----See: American Civil Liberties Union (WW)
Robinson, Bill (Bojangles)
----See: Robinson, Bill, material re (WW)
Rope and Faggot, by Walter White
----See: Pearl, Raymond (WW)
----Keith, Sir Arthur (WW)
Schuyler, George Samuel, the childhood of
----See: Schuyler, George Samuel (WW)
Scottsboro case
----See: Alexander, William W. (WW)
----Darrow, Clarence (WW)
----Beddow, Roderick (WW)
----[Spingarn?] Arthur (WW)
Senate of the United States, Movements for anti-filibuster and cloture rules
----See: Sorenson, Theodore (WW)
----Taft, Robert A. (WW)
----Vandenburg, Arthur H. (WW)
Segregation, in public schools
----See: Segregation, material re (WW)
South Carolina, Charleston, the Negro and the Y.M.C.A.
----See: McCray, John Henry (WW)
South Carolina, lynching and Ku Klux Klan
----See: McLeod, Thomas G. (WW)
Strange Fruit, by Lillian Smith - stage production of,
----See: Lillian Smith (WW)
Tobias Channing--manuscript by--The Use of Power in Securing Civil Rights.
----See: Tobias, Channing H. (WW)
Toklas, Alice B. "Cooking With Cognac," photocopy of typewritten
----article (eight pages)
----See: Toklas, Alice (PCW)
Town Meeting of the Air, "Memorandum on 'Round The World Town Meeting
----of the Air," by Walter White
----See: Town Hall of the Air (WW)
Tennessee Valley Authority and the Negro
----See: Bond, J. Max (WW)
Town Hall of the Air
----See: Acheson, Dean (WW)
----Town Hall of the Air (WW)
Tuberculosis among blacks,
----See: Arkansas Tuberculosis Association (WW)
Virgin Islands, the governorship of
----See: Bough, James A. (WW)
Virgin Islands, public relations, internal development, status of
----See: Chapman, Oscar (WW)
----de Castro, Morris F. (WW)
----Looby Z. Alexander (WW)
----Rosenblum, Harry (WW)
Virgin Islands, return of Income Taxes to
----See: Chapman, Oscar (WW)
----Rosenblum, Harry (WW)
----Hastie, William (WW)
Virgin Islands, publicity for
----See: Walter White (1947) (PCW)
"What Can I Do," sketch of proposed article by Walter White
----See: Roosevelt, Eleanor (WW)
[White] Citizens Councils, Mississippi, economic pressure used against blacks
----See: Eisenhower, Dwight David (WW)
White, Walter, appointment to the N.A.A.C.P.
----See: Johnson, James Weldon (WW)
----Washington, Edgar H. (WW)